Hell Pass!
Hell Pass! Dream State!
Hell Pass !Hell Pass!
Hell Pass!
All of
Heaps ya!
Heaps!
Seems I've climbed aboard a
ship with a storm for a captain!
Bah!
What luck I have!
You certainly are a
handful, aren't you, Luffy?
I love it!
Your dream is great!
I love it! Oh, yeah?
I'm so happy!
Oh, hey, easy there, buddy!
Crazy, but it's just perfect for you.
No way that's gonna happen until
you're King of the Pirates, though.
Better get cracking.
One more road poneglyph to Laugh Tale.
We're in the homestretch, everybody!
Perhaps so, but it won't
be an easy stretch.
We have a dangerous journey ahead.
The last road Poneglyph will be
the most difficult one to find.
Not to mention, we don't have
a single lead to follow up on.
Unlike the others, no one has
been able to find this Poneglyph.
We're sailing straight
into uncharted waters.
It's Flame Emperor Sabo!
He's calling the Kamabaka Queendom!
Good!
We'll hunt him down!
Let's trace that call, men!
The signal's not being jammed.
That's strange.
Why isn't he using a white
transponder snail to keep us out?
It must be an emergency call!
We better make this quick!
We need to get his location
before he hangs up!
We can't let this leak go!
The trace was successful.
Where is it from?
The kingdom of Lulusia.
From Lulusia.
Well, well.
We've been informed that
the insurgents in Lulusia
successfully overthrew
the country's monarchy.
at the start of the
Eight Nation Revolution.
It's the perfect place for Sabo to hide.
Then it's settled.
Sabo's quite the unlucky fellow.
It's not luck.
This is his destiny.
I'm fine.
Just glad I got through.
I'm glad too.
Yeah, me too!
But you sure took your sweet time calling!
What was the big hold-up?
Darling, I've been worried sick about you!
How can you do this to your dear friend?
I'm sorry, everyone.
You stop that!
You stop the police asking right now!
I have a feeling it's a
bit too early to celebrate.
You didn't call just to let
us know you're alive, did you?
So, what's the lowdown?
For starters, you read the article, right?
So you probably have
some questions for me.
Dragon.
It's true that King Cobra is dead.
I didn't kill him.
I knew it!
We never doubted you, Sabo!
We always believed in
you by innocent love!
Before I fled from Marie Joie, I
saw something I still can't believe.
What did you see, Sabo?
What's going on?
Never seen clouds like that.
No, that isn't a cloud.
There's something floating up there.
You insects will pay for this treachery!
You think the navy won't hear of this?
They'll burn you at the stake
and entail what's left of you!
Father, let me scold the traitors too!
Prepare to be eradicated, vermin!
Lord Zeki, please just listen!
This revolt has been a long
time coming, can't you see?
This wouldn't have happened if you
had thought of your people's welfare!
What?!
Why should the king waste his time
thinking about a bunch of lonely pedants?
You know your place, you insolent worms!
All we want is for you
to admit your wrongs!
Please, my lord, we won't
hurt you, I swear, just...
Get me out of this cage. No!
I was still at the reverie at
the time, in Pangaea Castle.
And I saw the empty throne.
Communications, cut off
your transponder snail. Huh?
Do I need to repeat myself?
Sorry, sir.
They always say that there's
no king of the world,
so no one is supposed to sit there.
Communications, listen carefully.
You did not trace any calls
today, do you understand?
Yeah, but I'm scared!
You didn't overhear a single word.
And as for Lulucyan...
I've never heard of it.
In fact, it never existed.
What's happening now?
Sabo?
Are you there?
A major Squad just hit
up the southeast coast!
Make emergency preparations!
A tsunami is coming!
We're all going to die!
It's freezing!
This is a nightmare!
Someone help!
Don't kill me again!
We talked about this!
What kind of madness is this?
Hey, aren't you cold without a shirt on?
I'm fine.
Feeling hot or cold is all in your head.
Oh, I see.
So your head's well insulated
because it's full of moss.
What's that?
You think you're cold?
Wait till I throw you in the ocean!
Let's see you try!
Could you two possibly
take a worse time to argue?
Jeep A!
Watch out for icebergs! Roger!
Furl the sails quickly!
The winds are far too strong!
Oh, you heard the man.
Let's go!
Strong run!
Take up the pace, Mosshead!
You're holding me back!
You really like the sound of
your own voice, don't you?
Tommy, do you see any land?
No, not yet, but we should
come up on an island soon.
With this snow, I'm assuming we're
probably within range of a winter island.
And it must be one with an
especially harsh climate.
Seems like they're having a hard time.
I'd better go help. How cute.
I love the hat. Looking good.
With this woven headpiece
that Otama bestowed upon me,
the falling snow shall prove no peril.
Hey, Nami!
Don't get this out!
Yeah, what?
What is that thing?
Looks like a warm eddy of
considerable size! No way!
That's an eddy! Oh, great! What now?
That thing's huge!
How is an eddy floating
in the air like that?
Concentratedly!
It must have warmed up so much
that it rose above the sea!
There's no way that's right!
Like a big, beautiful afro...
Get away, Jinpei!
It'll suck us in!
Leave it to me! Wait!
There's someone floating
up there in the water
Oh, what?
You think there's a mermaid?
Whoa, what's that?
I think Loopy's right.
I heard a little girl crying out.
You heard that from underwater?
What the hell's going on?
Even if there is someone, what can we do?
I'll just cut him out.
If you put so much as a scratch on that
girl, I swear I'm going to fillet your ass.
Like I would miss.
Here we go.
One sword style.
Bird dance!
Recapi-e!
Itings, comrades! I heard
a fuss. What ails thee?
Worry not!
Well, then hat-jumper-ay-man is here to...
To ensure our stuff!
Why did you stay inside?
You had it all and you
threw it all the way!
Stop it!
Hold on!
Thanks, Lupi!
Oh, give me a break, not you two!
What the hell are they doing?
Come on!
There's a little kid up there!
Who is that?
Who's there?
Thank you.
Where's the monster?
She's okay.
That's a relief. But, uh...
They're kind of just floating
up there, aren't they?
Hold up.
She's yelling something.
Stop!
Look down!
She said look down.
What is that thing?
We need to get out of here now, sail away!
Is this how it ends for us?
Jinbei! Hurry!
Come on, Jinbei!
Step on it! Let's go!
You can't leave it to me!
Move it!
What the hell is that thing?
I thought it was a shark,
but it's way too big.
And it looks like it's made of metal!
Hold on tight!
We're about to hit the water!
This isn't cool!
They fell straight into the sea!
I need to go now!
Franky!
Take the helm for me!
I'm going after them!
Bring the ship around to us!
No problem!
I got your back, bro!
I said no problem, but
these waters are rough.
We can't find them.
Well, I got some tricks up my sleeve.
Ship's bottom!
Rapid screw!
Up to it, baby!
Alright!
Frankie's coming for you,
bros, don't you worry!
Luffy! Chopper!
Stupid snow! I can't see!
Freaky! Move!
We got torpedoes!
Help me! Love me!
Oh, crap!
It's gonna capsize!
It sounded like there was
an explosion up above.
Chobro, move it.
I'm almost there.
You're going to be all right.
We're nearly to the surface.
You'll be safe soon.
I won't let you die.
This current is far too strong.
The Sunny can't navigate through this.
Thanks, Jimmy.
You saved us.
Well, there's no need to worry anymore.
Now we just have to find
our way back to the sun.
Nothing wrong, GP.
Hold on, charge.
We'll head for the seafloor.
Everyone take a deep breath while you can!
We're going under!
Here we go!
Damn it!
The current's way too fast!
We can't surface!
We're all gonna drown!
Why am I into water?
What the hell's going on?!
Hang in there, Robin!
Nami!
This ain't good.
We gotta come up with something fast.
Though we're all dead.
Hi, everyone.
I'm back.
Are you ready for your medicine?
One cup each.
Drink it up.
Okay, fine.
I'm gonna drink it, but
only for you, Toshiki.
That's a good boy.
Sorry, guys, but you'll have
to drink every last drop.
This tastes weird.
It's gross. I hate it.
Be brave. You can do it.
Do I really gotta drink the whole glass?
Yeah, then you'll turn
back to your normal size.
All right, if you say it'll
fix me, then I'll drink too.
Tashigi!
What do you think?
Do I look smaller?
You look great, Mock. It's working.
Does that mean I can go home soon? Uh-huh.
Just keep up the good work.
You're almost there.
Tashigi!
Vice Admiral Dole.
Can I borrow you for a sec?
Helmepo is driving everyone crazy.
Come on, can you please talk to him?
Look, I'm sorry, but I can't help you.
He has every right to be
worried about his friend.
And I see why.
We all wish we could
do something for Kobe.
Do something for Kobe!
He's our brother in arms,
but we can't let him die!
Both of us are on our knees begging you.
Gobi has been so good to me.
He deserves better than this.
We have to go to Pirate
Island before it's too late.
Please, Prince.
If you won't help us, we'll
have to go by ourselves.
Please have a heart.
I'm sorry, but I won't move an
inch until you promise to help us.
If you really expect to waltz into
Blackbeard's turf and come back alive,
you'd be picking a fight with an emperor.
Place is a death trap.
You poke the hive and
you're gonna get swarmed.
A whole horde of bloodthirsty
pirates will shoot you up.
That's why they call it Full of Lead.
Egghead's pretty close to here, you know.
We can take the seraphim, too!
You've lost your mind.
No way in hell, okay?
Let's all just calm down.
I wish we could contact
Drake with that shot, too.
There's nothing we can do.
Try to understand.
Kobe!
What you seriously don't know who I am?
Nope, no clue.
We're both part of the worst generation.
Stupid—did you just forget
me or everyone else too?
Oh, cool, you're the worst too. Huh, nice.
Don't
say it like that, you idiot!
idiot
I was there at Sabaody, too,
you know, two years back.
The name is Bonnie.
We're rivals. You got that?
That aside, you still saved my life.
So thanks for that.
Aw, hey, don't mention it, Bonnie.
Bonnie, damn it!
Cut that out, Luffy!
Stop it!
It's cold!
Now I'm immune to your wicked waterways.
Well, I'm immune to your immunity. Watch!
This guy is an emperor?
By the way, why is your
wanted poster so weird?
I thought your hair turned white.
The newspapers made a big deal out of it.
Oh, yeah? That's funny.
That's just how I look
when I'm totally free.
Oh, forget I asked.
So what happened to your friends?
Think they're okay?
I'm sure they're fine.
And what about your crew?
I didn't see your ship out there either.
I came here alone.
As for my ship, it got gobbled
up by that giant monster.
Stupid metal bastard.
I'm sorry to hear it.
Man, I really gotta find me some grub.
Actually, I'm hungry too.
No good place to eat.
Good idea.
Let's find some money
and head to a restaurant.
What?
Are you guys stupid?
There's no restaurants here.
This island belongs to the government.
Let me fill you in.
They call this place Egghead Island. Dr.
Vegapunk's lab is here, and
thanks to his inventions,
they say this island is
500 years in the future.
Dr. Vegapunk?
I've heard that name before.
I'm here to give him a piece of my mind.
We've got business.
Is everyone here? Are you all right?
Did the Sonny survive all that?
It's...
it's...
The giant robot!
But who is operating it?
Careful here, they come.
That was a bust.
Where did I go wrong this time?
Guess, I can't code the
instincts out of a living thing.
Whatever, I'll work on that. I don't.
I don't know who you are, but thanks!
You saved our asses!
I owe you one!
Hardly.
I'm just here to
troubleshoot my mecha-shark.
All I ordered that hunky-junk
to do was scout, report,
and bombard, not eat the target and
destroy all their frickin' valuables.
Must be a programming error.
What?!
You filthy pirates really
thought I came to save you?!
A genius government scientist like me
has no business with the likes of you!
My name is Dr. Vegapunk!
What?!
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
Thank you.